<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="first_draweritem">About</string>
    <string name="second_draweritem">Instructions</string>
    <string name="third_subitem1">College of ICT</string>
    <string name="third_subitem2">School of Law</string>
    <string name="third_draweritem">Building Information</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_4">Report Problem</string>
    <string name="language">Language:</string>
    <string name="permissions_denied">Cannot load maps without all the permissions granted</string>
    <string name="Permission_GPS">Please enable GPS to get your location</string>
    <string name="sub_item_3">College of Economic</string>
    <string-array name="languages">
        <item>Select Language</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Vietnamese</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="buildings_desc">
        <item>Select a destination…</item>
        <item>College of Information &amp; Communication Technology: formerly the Center for Informatics and Electronics (1990), was established in 1994. The total number of staff members is 94 with 24 Ph.D (5 associate professors), 51 masters. 3,362 undergraduate and 19 postgraduate students find their home in CICT.</item>
        <item>College of Economics: College of Economics (CE) is one of the largest school of CTU. Since its founding on July 30th, 1979, CE has been improving and developing itself. It has not stopped growing in size and improving the quality of training activities to meet the demand for human resources and research. It also provides advisory services to develop education, economic and social in the Mekong Delta.</item>
        <item>School of Law: School of Law (SoL) was established in February 2000 and originated from the Department of Law, which was established in September 1998. The SoL aims at training human resources in law for the Mekong Delta. The School provides training and enrichment programs for provincial judicial officials. Scientific research is also highly promoted. In 2011, the SoL initiated a graduate program for Master of Business Law.</item>
        <item>College of Agriculture &amp; Applied Biology: The College of Agriculture (COA), formerly called Faculty of Agriculture, was founded in 1968 in CanTho City, two years after the foundation of Cantho University. By 1975, the COA had admitted 7 academic batches and trained more than 300 graduated engineers.  Since the Liberation (1975), 21 new batches have been graduated with degrees in Animal Husbandry and Veterinary, Aquaculture, Food Processing, Agriculture Engineering, and Agricultural Economics. Later on, these new degree programs became independent faculties. With the restructuring of the University in 1996, the Faculties of Agronomy, Animal Husbandry and Veterinary, and Food Technology were merged into the COA.</item>
        <item>College of Aquaculture &amp; Fisheries: The College of Aquaculture and Fisheries (CAF), Can Tho University (CTU), was established in 1979. For over 30 years, CAF has been always attempting and developing itself to fulfill its missions of education, research and technical transfer on the areas of aquaculture and fisheries in order to meet the need of manpower and advanced technology for the development of aquaculture and fisheries in Viet Nam,  and the Mekong Delta, particularly.</item>
        <item>College of Engineering Technology: As one of the major unit of the University of Can Tho, College of Engineering Technology is responsible for training, conducting research and transferring technology in engineering for the Mekong Delta region and country.</item>
        <item>College of Environment &amp; Natural Resources: The College of Environment and Natural Resources (CENRes), established according to Decision No.81/QĐ-ĐHCT in 2008, is one of the educational and research institutions in Can Tho University. The college conducts its programs and activities guided by Vision, Missions and Core Values of the university.</item>
        <item>College of Natural Sciences: Based upon the Decision 1242/QĐ-ĐHCT dated 14 August 2009, College of Sciences was renamed as College of Natural Science (CNS). Currently, CNS hosts 6 graduate programs and 4 undergraduate programs covering the fields of natural sciences such as mathematics, physics, chemistry and biology which contribute greatly to the training of scientific human resources for the development of the Mekong Delta as well as the whole country.</item>
        <item>Administration Building: Administration Building includes Department of Political Affairs, Department of Student Assistance, Department of Academic Affairs, Department of International Relations, Department of Administration and Planning, Department of Research Affairs, Department of Facility, Department of Financial Affairs, Department of Legality, Department of Personnel, Cooperative Training Center, Information and Network  Management Center, Quality Management Center.</item>
        <item>Learning Resource Center:  Learning Resource Center - Can Tho University, formerly known as Can Tho University Central Library, was sponsored by Atlantic Philanthropies (USA) to build a new building on the basis of transferring about 70% of the document capital and the whole staff of the Central Library to the Learning Resource Center. The Learning Learning Center is located on a land area of ​​7,560 m2 right at the entrance to the main entrance of Zone II, Can Tho University, an ideal location convenient for customers to use the Learning Resource Center to serve study and research. LRC was built 4 floors with a total usable area of 7.200 m2 . The Learning Resource Center is designed to construct and arrange each floor of the building very attractive and scientific suitable for each corner of study, research, independent and team work. Especially, the scientific arrangement of the operation line of organization, administration and customer service, creates flexibility and ease for customers to use the Learning Resource Center</item>
        <item>School of Political Science: The predecessor of the School of Political Science, the Marxist-Lenin Committee, was established in October 1975. By 1978, according to the decision of the Ministry of Education and Training and Can Tho University, Mar-Leni Committee developed into the Faculty of Marxism-Lenin, including 04 subjects: Marxist-Leninist Philosophy, Political Economics Marxist-Lenin, Scientific Socialism and History of the Communist Party of Vietnam. In 1987, the Faculty of Marx-Lenin was renamed to the Department of Marxist-Lenin. In March 2003, the Ministry of Education and Training decided to establish the Faculty of Marxism-Leninism and Ho Chi Minh Thought Center under Can Tho University on the basis of the Marxist-Lenin Department. In October 2008, the Faculty of Marxism-Leninism and Ho Chi Minh Thought was renamed into the School of Political Science.</item>
        <item>School of Social Sciences &amp; Humanities: School of Social Sciences and Humanities was established in September 2009 on the basis of the separation from the School of Education and Learning Resources Center (LRC). The School has the tasks of training and researching in the field of social sciences and humanities for the development of the Mekong Delta region and the whole country. From April 2015 the Department of English and Department of French were separated to School of Foreign Languages. The School of Social Sciences and Humanities remains four Departments: Department of Vietnamese Linguistics and Literature, Department of History – Geography and Tourism, Department of Library and Information Management, Department of Sociology; and four Bachelor majors: Vietnam Studies (tour guide), Literature, Information , Sociology and one Master program: Vietnamese Literature. In the near future, the School is going to offer the new majors: Journalism and Cultural Studies.</item>
        <item>School of Education: The Faculty of Pedagogy was one of the first four units of Can Tho University (now Can Tho University), which was established on March 31, 1966. After 1975, the Faculty of Pedagogy was split into a Faculty. It is Nature and the Department of Social Education with the mission of training high school teachers. After that, these two faculties continued to split into 5 Faculties: Math - Physics (1980), Chemistry - Biology (10), History - Geography (1982), Literature (1983) and Foreign Language (1983). 30 years later, in 1996, the Faculty of Education was re-established on the basis of the Faculties.</item>
        <item>Department of Physical Education: Department of Physical Education of Can Tho University, teaching physical education and sports for specialized and non-specialized students of physical education, conducting scientific research activities and organizing activities Sports movement for the development of education and training and physical training for the Mekong Delta region.</item>
        <item>School of Pre-University: The National Preparatory School was established on October 26, 2007 to meet the needs of training and developing the contingent of scientific and technical personnel of ethnic minorities, people in remote, deep-lying, border and island areas for provinces in the Mekong Delta region.</item>
        <item>Dormitory A</item>
        <item>Dormitory B</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="buildings_desc_long">
        <item>Select a destination…</item>
        <item>Vision\n
CICT’s main missions are to offer undergraduate and postgraduate programs, and to participate in scientific research and technology transfer in the field of Information and Communication Technology (ICT).
CICT’s vision towards 2020 is to become a well-known ICT research and education institution in Vietnam, which plays a core role in ICT research, education and technology transfer in the Mekong Delta and the Southern Region, and reaches the training standards from the advanced universities in the world.\n\n
Courses\n
            CICT consists of 5 academic departments and 2 supporting units:\n
1. Department of Information Systems\n
2. Department of Computer Network and Communications\n
3. Department of Software Engineering\n
4. Department of Computer Science\n
5. Department of Information Technology\n
6. Administration Office\n
7. Electronics-Informatics Center\n\n

From its inception, the College was one of the seven key ICT faculties in Vietnam and has been hugely invested in programs and projects such as the National Target Program on Information Technology, and the Capacity Building Project in Undergraduate and Postgraduate training.
The College has a strong collaboration with the Association of French-speaking Universities (AUF) in the Bilingual Information Technology program (French instruction) to train IT being-engineers with good French communication skills. The College is actively working towards co-operating with foreign universities toofer at least one advanced undergraduate program and one advanced master program.
The College conducts effective scientific research and education cooperation with multiple partners such as the University of Nantes, the University of La Rochelle (France), the French Institute for Research &amp; Development (IRD), the French Institute of Informatics (IFI, Hanoi), the University of Kemi-Tornio (Finland), etc.
Various research projects have been successfully executed. Efforts are made to increase CICT’s training scale, to improve the quality of its academic staff, to upgrade the facilities, and to search for more collaboration opportunities.\n\n
College strengths:\n
E-learning and distance education\n
Geographic Information Systems (GIS)\n
Data mining and pattern recognition\n
Modeling and simulation\n
Big data and cloud computing\n
Network and system security\n
Mobile communications\n\n

Undergraduate programs:\n
Information Systems\n
Software Engineering\n
Communications and Computer Networks\n
Computer Science\n
Information Technology\n\n
Special bilingual program (French-Vietnamese) for all of the above disciplines.\n\n
Postgraduate programs:\n
Master of Information Systems\n
Master of Computer Science\n
Ph.D of Information Systems.</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="buildings_name">
        <item>Select a destination…</item>
        <item>College of Information &amp; Communication Technology</item>
        <item>College of Economics</item>
        <item>School of Law</item>
        <item>College of Agriculture &amp; Applied Biology</item>
        <item>College of Aquaculture &amp; Fisheries</item>
        <item>College of Engineering Technology</item>
        <item>College of Environment &amp; Natural Resources</item>
        <item>College of Natural Sciences</item>
        <item>Administration Building</item>
        <item>Learning Resource Center</item>
        <item>School of Political Science</item>
        <item>School of Social Sciences &amp; Humanities</item>
        <item>School of Education</item>
        <item>Department of Physical Education</item>
        <item>School of Pre-University</item>
        <item>Dormitory A</item>
        <item>Dormitory B</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>