<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="first_draweritem">About</string>
    <string name="second_draweritem">Instructions</string>
    <string name="third_subitem1">College of ICT</string>
    <string name="third_subitem2">School of Law</string>
    <string name="third_draweritem">Building Information</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_4">Report Problem</string>
    <string name="language">Language:</string>
    <string name="permissions_denied">Cannot load maps without all the permissions granted</string>
    <string name="Permission_GPS">Please enable GPS to get your location</string>
    <string name="sub_item_3">College of Economic</string>
    <string-array name="languages">
        <item>Select Language</item>
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Vietnamese</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="buildings_desc">
        <item>Select a destination…</item>
        <item>College of Information &amp; Communication Technology: formerly the Center for Informatics and Electronics (1990), was established in 1994. The total number of staff members is 94 with 24 Ph.D (5 associate professors), 51 masters. 3,362 undergraduate and 19 postgraduate students find their home in CICT.</item>
        <item>College of Economics: College of Economics (CE) is one of the largest school of CTU. Since its founding on July 30th, 1979, CE has been improving and developing itself. It has not stopped growing in size and improving the quality of training activities to meet the demand for human resources and research. It also provides advisory services to develop education, economic and social in the Mekong Delta.</item>
        <item>School of Law: School of Law (SoL) was established in February 2000 and originated from the Department of Law, which was established in September 1998. The SoL aims at training human resources in law for the Mekong Delta. The School provides training and enrichment programs for provincial judicial officials. Scientific research is also highly promoted. In 2011, the SoL initiated a graduate program for Master of Business Law.</item>
        <item>College of Agriculture &amp; Applied Biology: The College of Agriculture (COA), formerly called Faculty of Agriculture, was founded in 1968 in CanTho City, two years after the foundation of Cantho University. By 1975, the COA had admitted 7 academic batches and trained more than 300 graduated engineers.  Since the Liberation (1975), 21 new batches have been graduated with degrees in Animal Husbandry and Veterinary, Aquaculture, Food Processing, Agriculture Engineering, and Agricultural Economics. Later on, these new degree programs became independent faculties. With the restructuring of the University in 1996, the Faculties of Agronomy, Animal Husbandry and Veterinary, and Food Technology were merged into the COA.</item>
        <item>College of Aquaculture &amp; Fisheries: The College of Aquaculture and Fisheries (CAF), Can Tho University (CTU), was established in 1979. For over 30 years, CAF has been always attempting and developing itself to fulfill its missions of education, research and technical transfer on the areas of aquaculture and fisheries in order to meet the need of manpower and advanced technology for the development of aquaculture and fisheries in Viet Nam,  and the Mekong Delta, particularly.</item>
        <item>College of Engineering Technology: As one of the major unit of the University of Can Tho, College of Engineering Technology is responsible for training, conducting research and transferring technology in engineering for the Mekong Delta region and country.</item>
        <item>College of Environment &amp; Natural Resources: The College of Environment and Natural Resources (CENRes), established according to Decision No.81/QĐ-ĐHCT in 2008, is one of the educational and research institutions in Can Tho University. The college conducts its programs and activities guided by Vision, Missions and Core Values of the university.</item>
        <item>College of Natural Sciences: Based upon the Decision 1242/QĐ-ĐHCT dated 14 August 2009, College of Sciences was renamed as College of Natural Science (CNS). Currently, CNS hosts 6 graduate programs and 4 undergraduate programs covering the fields of natural sciences such as mathematics, physics, chemistry and biology which contribute greatly to the training of scientific human resources for the development of the Mekong Delta as well as the whole country.</item>
        <item>Administration Building: Administration Building includes Department of Political Affairs, Department of Student Assistance, Department of Academic Affairs, Department of International Relations, Department of Administration and Planning, Department of Research Affairs, Department of Facility, Department of Financial Affairs, Department of Legality, Department of Personnel, Cooperative Training Center, Information and Network  Management Center, Quality Management Center.</item>
        <item>Learning Resource Center:  Learning Resource Center - Can Tho University, formerly known as Can Tho University Central Library, was sponsored by Atlantic Philanthropies (USA) to build a new building on the basis of transferring about 70% of the document capital and the whole staff of the Central Library to the Learning Resource Center. The Learning Learning Center is located on a land area of ​​7,560 m2 right at the entrance to the main entrance of Zone II, Can Tho University, an ideal location convenient for customers to use the Learning Resource Center to serve study and research. LRC was built 4 floors with a total usable area of 7.200 m2 . The Learning Resource Center is designed to construct and arrange each floor of the building very attractive and scientific suitable for each corner of study, research, independent and team work. Especially, the scientific arrangement of the operation line of organization, administration and customer service, creates flexibility and ease for customers to use the Learning Resource Center</item>
        <item>School of Political Science: The predecessor of the School of Political Science, the Marxist-Lenin Committee, was established in October 1975. By 1978, according to the decision of the Ministry of Education and Training and Can Tho University, Mar-Leni Committee developed into the Faculty of Marxism-Lenin, including 04 subjects: Marxist-Leninist Philosophy, Political Economics Marxist-Lenin, Scientific Socialism and History of the Communist Party of Vietnam. In 1987, the Faculty of Marx-Lenin was renamed to the Department of Marxist-Lenin. In March 2003, the Ministry of Education and Training decided to establish the Faculty of Marxism-Leninism and Ho Chi Minh Thought Center under Can Tho University on the basis of the Marxist-Lenin Department. In October 2008, the Faculty of Marxism-Leninism and Ho Chi Minh Thought was renamed into the School of Political Science.</item>
        <item>School of Social Sciences &amp; Humanities: School of Social Sciences and Humanities was established in September 2009 on the basis of the separation from the School of Education and Learning Resources Center (LRC). The School has the tasks of training and researching in the field of social sciences and humanities for the development of the Mekong Delta region and the whole country. From April 2015 the Department of English and Department of French were separated to School of Foreign Languages. The School of Social Sciences and Humanities remains four Departments: Department of Vietnamese Linguistics and Literature, Department of History – Geography and Tourism, Department of Library and Information Management, Department of Sociology; and four Bachelor majors: Vietnam Studies (tour guide), Literature, Information , Sociology and one Master program: Vietnamese Literature. In the near future, the School is going to offer the new majors: Journalism and Cultural Studies.</item>
        <item>School of Education: The Faculty of Pedagogy was one of the first four units of Can Tho University (now Can Tho University), which was established on March 31, 1966. After 1975, the Faculty of Pedagogy was split into a Faculty. It is Nature and the Department of Social Education with the mission of training high school teachers. After that, these two faculties continued to split into 5 Faculties: Math - Physics (1980), Chemistry - Biology (10), History - Geography (1982), Literature (1983) and Foreign Language (1983). 30 years later, in 1996, the Faculty of Education was re-established on the basis of the Faculties.</item>
        <item>Department of Physical Education: Department of Physical Education of Can Tho University, teaching physical education and sports for specialized and non-specialized students of physical education, conducting scientific research activities and organizing activities Sports movement for the development of education and training and physical training for the Mekong Delta region.</item>
        <item>School of Pre-University: The National Preparatory School was established on October 26, 2007 to meet the needs of training and developing the contingent of scientific and technical personnel of ethnic minorities, people in remote, deep-lying, border and island areas for provinces in the Mekong Delta region.</item>
        <item>Dormitory A</item>
        <item>Dormitory B</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="buildings_desc_long">
        <item>Select a destination…</item>
        <item>Vision\n
            CICTs main missions are to offer undergraduate and postgraduate programs, and to participate in scientific research and technology transfer in the field of Information and Communication Technology (ICT).
CICTs vision towards 2020 is to become a well-known ICT research and education institution in Vietnam, which plays a core role in ICT research, education and technology transfer in the Mekong Delta and the Southern Region, and reaches the training standards from the advanced universities in the world.\n\n
Courses\n
            CICT consists of 5 academic departments and 2 supporting units:\n
1. Department of Information Systems\n
2. Department of Computer Network and Communications\n
3. Department of Software Engineering\n
4. Department of Computer Science\n
5. Department of Information Technology\n
6. Administration Office\n
7. Electronics-Informatics Center\n\n

From its inception, the College was one of the seven key ICT faculties in Vietnam and has been hugely invested in programs and projects such as the National Target Program on Information Technology, and the Capacity Building Project in Undergraduate and Postgraduate training.
The College has a strong collaboration with the Association of French-speaking Universities (AUF) in the Bilingual Information Technology program (French instruction) to train IT being-engineers with good French communication skills. The College is actively working towards co-operating with foreign universities toofer at least one advanced undergraduate program and one advanced master program.
The College conducts effective scientific research and education cooperation with multiple partners such as the University of Nantes, the University of La Rochelle (France), the French Institute for Research &amp; Development (IRD), the French Institute of Informatics (IFI, Hanoi), the University of Kemi-Tornio (Finland), etc.
Various research projects have been successfully executed. Efforts are made to increase CICTs training scale, to improve the quality of its academic staff, to upgrade the facilities, and to search for more collaboration opportunities.\n\n
College strengths:\n
E-learning and distance education\n
Geographic Information Systems (GIS)\n
Data mining and pattern recognition\n
Modeling and simulation\n
Big data and cloud computing\n
Network and system security\n
Mobile communications\n\n

Undergraduate programs:\n
Information Systems\n
Software Engineering\n
Communications and Computer Networks\n
Computer Science\n
Information Technology\n\n
Special bilingual program (French-Vietnamese) for all of the above disciplines.\n\n
Postgraduate programs:\n
Master of Information Systems\n
Master of Computer Science\n
Ph.D of Information Systems.</item>
        <item>
* Vision\n\n
CE strives to become one of the top colleges of CTU in particular and of Vietnam in general and strives to become a college with intensive curriculum and scientific research in quality in the Mekong Delta, Vietnam and Asia-Pacific by 2022.\n\n

* Mission\n\n
The CE is a training center for high-quality human resources in the area of economy and business in the region, meeting Vietnamese and international standards. The CE is also a research and consultancy center for economic and business issues, solving problems in the development of business and management organizations and the socio-economic development.\n\n
* Goals\n\n
Respond to high-priority issues facing society in agribusiness (including food, supplying inputs, processing products, and marketing), natural resources, environmental quality, and communities.\n
Teach students how to use economic and business principles and develop their leadership and communication skills to prepare them for employment and to continue life-long learning.\n
Conduct applied research programs to analyze business and public policy issues and respond to high-priority societal needs.\n
Enhance the use of economic principles and research methods in solving economic problems through disciplinary research and graduate education.\n
Develop targeted extension and outreach educational programs to deliver relevant information and teach the use of economic and business principles in making decisions.\n
Collaborate with scientists and educators in other disciplines to incorporate economic analysis into multi-disciplinary programs.\n
Develop a network with former students to enhance student learning experiences and placement and to facilitate achievement of Department goals.\n
Create a professional environment conducive to promoting teamwork among faculty, staff, and students as they strive for excellence in the pursuit of the Departments goals.\n\n
ACTIVITIES\n\n
* Research\n
Research and consulting areas: enterprise development, research of domestic and foreign markets, project management and evaluation, agricultural planning and rural development.\n
Planning on development of socio-economic, agriculture, rural areas and restructuring crops and livestock.\n
Improving the economic models of households in the Mekong Delta;\n
Research of competitive advantage and comparative advantage in some important sectors in the Mekong Delta to establish data banks for enterprises;\n
Assess business situation and propose solutions to support small and medium enterprises in the Mekong Delta\n
Research of the finance -banking\n
Supporting,consulting import-export business and trade promotion;\n
Environmental economics project.\n\n
* International cooperation\n
International cooperation in training and scientific research\n
SEBA has successfully cooperated with the Netherlands in MHO2 Program for the project "Upgrading teaching and research in Economics, Business and Law at Can Tho University".\n
Cooperate with the Netherlands – Nuffic for the project "Enhancing the Capability of Teaching and Research, Assisting Small and Medium Sized Enterprises and Farming Households".\n
The project "Distance Education for master degree in Economics" has been sponsored by VLIR Program (Belgium).\n
Some following projects have been implemented such as project on Seed Component (DANIDA), Agricultural Management and Rural Development - Spain Cooperative, GTZ project on Small &amp; Medium Enterprises Promotion (German), AUSAid (Australia); EEPSEA (Singapore), and other projects collaborated with Hungary, Australia, and Canada.\n\n
* Training activities and consulting, short-term training:\n\n
Training Activities\n
Undergraduate training programs\n
Accounting\n
Auditing\n
Finance and Banking\n
Corporate Finance\n
Business Administration\n
Marketing\n
Tourism and Service Management\n
Agricultural Economics\n
Commercial Management\n
Environmental and Resource Economics\n
International Business\n
Economics\n
Master training programs\n
Business Administration\n
Agricultural Economics\n
Finance – Banking\n\n
Phd training programs:\n
Agricultural Economics\n
Business Administration\n
Finance - Banking\n\n
Short-term training courses: Accounting, Auditing, Finance, Banking, Business Management, Marketing and Trade Services, Brand Development and Management, Sales Management, Hotel - Restaurant Management,Stock Trading, International Business, Project Management,...\n
From a school with one field of study at the beginning, it has developed into a multidisciplinary school. It has been improving and developing students and quality of education.\n
From its establishing, CE took in around 40 students each year. So far CE has had more than 1,000 students every year.\n
CE is focusing on improving curriculum and teaching methods in order to improve the quality of training.\n\n

Consultancy Activities, Short - Term Training:\n\n
Production Management, Quality Management; Supply Chain Management, building strategic business,Project Management.\n
The Enterprise Financial Analysis, Potential Market Analysis and Forecasting; Stock Market.\n
Brand Development and Management; Marketing Strategy and Promotion Campaigns; Marketing Research and Method of Data Analysis; Communication and Negotiation.</item>

        <item>
Departments and Center\n\n
Department of Administrative Law\n
Department of Judicial Law\n
Department of Commercial Law\n
Center for Comparative Law\n\n
Education and Training\n\n
    Bachelor programs\n\n
Administrative Law\n
Judicial Law\n
Commercial Law\n
Master programs\n
Economic Law\n\n

Annually, the SoL admits more than 300 students in-campus, around 900 off- campus studying at the Community Colleges in the Mekong Delta provinces and about 40 graduate students.\n
The SoL has international relationships with institutions and universities of the Netherlands, France, Britain, Cambodia, Japan, Canada, the United States and so on.</item>

        <item>
*Vision\n\n
 - To offer Undergraduate, Masters, and Ph.D. training programs of Agriculture to meet current and  future educational needs of the residents in the Mekong Delta.\n
- To conduct fundamental scientific research and to develop applications of agriculture
- To directly serve the needs of the community by spreading knowledge of science and technology and transferring technology of agriculture.\n
- To assist in developing the regional economy and local productivity by expanding agriculture, and bringing scientific and technological advances to local producers\n\n

Specialized disciplines \n\n
The COA consists of the following 8 departments and 1 administration office:\n
1.      Crop Sciences\n
2.      Soil Sciences\n
3.      Plant Protection\n
4.      Food Technology\n
5.      Animal Sciences\n
6.      Veterinary Medicine\n
7.      Administration Office\n
8.      Biochemistry - Plant Physiology Department\n
9.      Department of Agriculture Genetics and Breeding Environmental\n\n
Personals: 257 Staff; 121 Lecturers; 65 researchers and 26 others; in which: 35 Ass. Prof. 05;Prof, 74 Doctors; 76 Masters\n\n

Undergraduate training program\n\n
Up to now, the COA has trained more than 15,000 agricultural engineers for the Mekong Delta (MD). Many of them occupy key positions in government offices, companies, and business enterprises. Some are notably successful in their own agricultural private companies.\n
In order to meet the ever-increasing labour force requirement in the MD, the COA has been actively expanding its degree courses and personnel competence.  Academic curriculums have been appropriately adjusted to correspond with students basic and specialised knowledge. This provides them the experience on actual situations as part of their training. This in turn, gives them a positive view of practical production situations with will be useful in their future work.
At present, the COA is able to yearly admit around 1600 students and provide them with engineering training in Agriculture, Agronomy, Animal Sciences, Veterinary Medicine, Food Technology, Land Management, Soil sciences, Plant protection and  Sciences. Students of the COA are given many opportunities to study and self –develop. Many scholarships sponsored by study extended to outstanding student and to those in financial need.\n\n

Postgraduate program    \n\n
Furthering university-training programs, COA offers postgraduate programs for Master’s degrees in the fields of Agriculture, Soil Sciences, Animal husbandry-Veterinary Medicine, Veterinary Medicine, Environmental Sciences, Food Technology and Plant protection; and PhD. degrees in the fields of Agriculture, Soil Sciences, Animal husbandry-Veterinary Medicine, and Plant protection.\n
Also, students of COA have made significant contributions to scientific research. Thanks to the knowledge attained, a good number of students’ research theses have been highly appreciated by the local and central government.\n\n

Domestic and International collaborations    \n\n
Domestic and international collaborations are one of the strengths of the COA. It co-operates with foreign universities and organisations as well as their provinces in the MD in areas of scientific research, training, and agricultural extension.\n
Domestic collaboration: Agricultural University 1, Soils and soil fertility Institute, NIAPP, Sub-NIAPP in HCM city, Mekong Delta Rice Research Institute, Southern Fruit Research Institute, Forestry and Agricultural University-HCM city, HCM City Tropical Biology Institute...\n
International Organizations: HEIFER, IRRI, OXFAM, FAO, UNDP, JICA, JIRCAS, DANIDA, SAREC, ACIAR, IUCN, UNEP, WWF,...</item>

        <item>
VISION \n
CAF with its good capacities will become a strong college to support CTU’s and national strategic plans to 2030 in aquaculture and fisheries.\n\n

MISSION \n
The generally major mandates of the College of Aquaculture and Fisheries are:\n\n
Offering undergraduate and graduate educational programs in the fields of aquaculture and fisheries.\n
Conducting researches related to aquaculture development, aquatic environment, fisheries resource management, and marine biodiversity.\n
Transferring technologies of aquaculture and fisheries to farmers and the commercial production sectors in the Mekong delta and related region\n\n

At present, CAF has 107 staffs, of which there are 61 instructors and 43 researchers, holding different titles and degrees (12 Associate professors, 34 PhD, and 41 Masters). CAF has 7 departments as follows:\n
Dept. of Applied Hydrobiology\n
Dept. of Aquatic Animal Pathology\n
Dept. of Aquatic Nutrition and Products Processing\n
Dept. of Freshwater Aquaculture\n
Dept. of Coastal Aquaculture\n
Dept. of Fisheries Management and Economics\n
Administrative Unit\n\n
CAF has a system of advanced laboratories, hatcheries, and field stations in both freshwater and brackish water areas to support education, research and technical transfer locally and internationally.\n
Since it was established, CAF has over 3,000 alumni. Currently, CAF has 1,700 undergraduates, 150 master and 30 PhD students. CAF currently offers 9 programs for Bachelor degree: Aquaculture; Aquatic Animal Pathology; Aquatic Resources Management; Fisheries Economics; Aquatic Products Processing; Mariculture and Marine Resources Conservation; and Advanced Program in Aquaculture (taught in English and 2 transferred programs from college to bachelor degree (Aquaculture and Aquatic Products Processing). CAF currently offer 2 programs for Master degree (Aquaculture and Aquatic Resources Management) and 1 programs for doctoral degree (Aquaculture)\n
In recent years (2006 – 2013), CAF has conducted more than 150 researches in different fields, published a large number of scientific papers and contributed significantly to the practical production and development of aquaculture and fisheries in the region.\n
CAF regularly offers training courses for national and international participants, especially on (i) seed production and farming of freshwater and brackish water species; (ii) live food culture and use; (iii) water quality analysis and pond management; (iv) fish nutrition analysis and feeding formulation in aquaculture; and (v) fish and crustacean disease analysis, diagnosis and treatment.</item>

        <item>
Mission\n
The mission of the College of Engineering Technology is:\n\n
To provide high quality human resources in engineering technology,\n
To carry out scientific research and technology transfer for serving the sustainable development of the Mekong Delta and Viet Nam,\n
To undertake and perform social responsibility and community services.\n\n
Vision\n
By 2022, the College of Engineering Technology targets to become one of the leading organizations in training, research, and innovation in Vietnam and South East Asia.</item>

        <item>
Vision\n
Can Tho University targets to be one of the leading higher education institutions in Vietnam and recognized as one of the top universities in Asia-Pacific in training and research in 2022.\n\n
Missions\n
Can Tho University operates its resources to be the leading national institution for education, research and technology transfer, making significant contributions to the development of high quality human resources, fostering the talents and the advancement of science and technology to cater for the regional and national socio-economic development. Can Tho University is the crucial driving force for the development of the Mekong Delta region.\n\n
Core Values\n\n
Consensus - Devotion - Quality – Innovation.\n\n
In order to gain good achievements in scientific research and technology transfer in the Vietnamese Mekong Delta, the CENRes has strengthened itself, especially in the following fields: Biodiversity conservation, environmental quality assessment, environmental toxicology, waste water and solid waste treatment in urban areas, water resource engineering, environmental impact assessment, strategic environment, environment management, land-use planning and GIS applications.\n
Intensive researches are to support the on-going educational programmes. In fact, different undergraduate and master and PhD projects have been successfully defended and many of them have been published in different national and international peer-review scientific journals.\n\n

Departments\n\n
At the moment (2018), there are five departments in CENRes, including:\n
Department of Environmental Sciences\n
Department of Environmental Engineering\n
Department of Environment Management\n
Department of Land Resources\n
Department of Water Resources</item>

        <item>
Facilities:\n\n
At the beginning, the College had a two-floor building consisting 12 laboratories for biology, chemistry, physics; 6 computer rooms; an administrative office. Most lab equipment was from the Netherlands. Now, CNS has 19 laboratories with modern machines and equipment, 1 computer room and 15 classrooms. Thanks to the capital of CTU as well as other projects, old facilities have been replaced year after year. In 2010, CTU invested to enlarge lab areas of the College by making a three-floor building with 22 rooms strongly supporting research and educational activities of the College.\n
At the recent, CNS has 4 Departments which are Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry and Biology and 1 Administrative office-Library.\n\n

Undergraduate Education\n\n
CNS started educating Biotechnology major course 27 from 2001 to 2006. Since the following years 2002, 2006, 2007, other bachelor majors of Chemistry, Applied Mathematics, and Biology have been opened. Since 2010 and 2014, two following bachelor programs including Medicinal Chemistry and Applied Physics have also been opened. \n
Beside the mission of teaching these majors, CNS is also responsible for teaching basic science subjects for students from various training programs of CTU such as Engineering, Information Technology and Agriculture.\n
At the College, students can practice in the labs or computer rooms after studying theory. In the third year of every program, the College organizes field trips for students to visit and study in companies, factories, research institutes, and other places related to their major. After the field trip, students will make reports and display specimens that were collected. These activities offer students useful knowledge and make lessons more realistic.\n
There are more than 100 students who get enough qualification and graduate from CNS each year. It supplies a large number of human resources for the Mekong delta.\n\n

Graduate Education\n\n
Since 2004, in the supporting from Professor Nguyen Van Hieu, CNS has started to offer graduate programs in Mathematics (Algebra and Number Theory; Analytic and Probability and Statistics), Chemistry (Theoretical and Physical Chemistry, Organic Chemistry), Physics (Applied Physics and Theoretical Physics) and Ecology. In collaboration with Universities and Institutes from HCM City, CNS is not only responsible for managing issues but also for teaching 70% of the programs and instructing graduate students doing these.\n
CNS now hosts more than 874 graduate students of all majors with the number of graduate students reaching almost 90% each course. These highly qualified human resources effectively support in socio-economic development of the Mekong Delta.</item>

        <item>Administration Building</item>

        <item>
Function\n\n
- Advising and assisting the Principal and Vice Rectors to collect, organize, exploit, store and provide information and materials services for teaching, learning and scientific research. study for civil servants, employees, employees and students working, studying at the University and other subjects in need.
Mission\n
1. To serve the needs of academic documents reference and research in learning, teaching and scientific research for the Mekong Delta region.\n
2. Coordinate with the Training Department to propose supplementing textbooks and reference materials for modules that have not yet been available, have few or are outdated.\n
3. Ensuring network security in scientific information search links under the units management.\n
4. Organize training courses on information skills for learners in lifelong research and learning.\n
5. To guide library operations and supplement information resources for the library system of Can Tho University.\n
6. Consulting and transferring library science and technology to the library system in the Mekong Delta.\n
7. Actively research and develop the library system development strategy to meet the development needs and improve the quality of training and scientific research of the University.\n
8. To establish new and maintain effective international relationships to improve the operational quality of the university library system.\n
9. Efficiently exploiting revenue-generating services contributes to improving the efficiency of library operations and the life of public servants and employees in the unit.\n
10. Print staff cards, students integrated with library cards for the whole school.\n
11. Organize the implementation of revenue generating conference and seminar services to improve the quality of operations and increase income for TTHL staff.\n
12. Support to improve the operational quality of the library system of colleges and universities in the Mekong Delta region.</item>

        <item>
*Mission\n\n
           - Training in Bachelor of Politics, Bachelor of Philosophy and Bachelors degree in full-time Citizenship Education;\n
           - Teaching political theory subjects for all majors of the whole school;\n
           - Teaching Philosophy to master students in majors throughout the school;\n
           - Scientific research on theoretical and practical issues to meet the training and solving practical issues raised today;\n
           - Advice to help the Party Committee and the Board of Directors in political education, ideas for staff and students.\n\n
Currently, the Faculty has 3 Divisions (Basic principles of Marxism-Leninism, Ho Chi Minhs Thought, Revolutionary ways of the Communist Party of Vietnam) and Faculty Office. The Faculty currently has 30 lecturers, including 8 Ph.Ds and 22 Masters (including 06 lecturers studying Research at home and abroad).</item>

        <item>
The task of quality assurance: The School established the group’s Quality Assurance Division and completed the task of self- quality assurance training. Appointing  officials involved in the group testing, assessing the quality of training programs in the University.\n\n

Scientific research work: School’s staff and students actively participating in scientific research activities with the results completed a lot of research projects at University level and Provincial level. In addition, the School staff also participate research projects with Bac Lieu University, Mekong Delta Research and Development, Can Tho City Council Social Sciences and Humanities and the subject of international cooperation, etc.…\n\n

International cooperation:the School often has programs in cooperation with the University and international educational organizations. Reception of professionals, volunteers abroad to work, teach and promote the cooperation and exchange of teachers and student programs at universities.\n\n
Units Of School\n\n
Administration Office\n
Department Of Vietnamese Linguistics And Literature\n
Department Of Sociology\n
Department Of Library And Information Management\n
Department Of History - Geography - Tourism</item>

        <item>
Missions:\n\n
Repairing teachers, educators and experts of education.\n\n
Undergraduate programs:\n
Elementary Teacher Education\n
Mathematics Teacher Education\n
Physics Teacher Education\n
Chemistry Teacher Education\n
Biology Teacher Education\n
Vietnamese Linguistic &amp; Literature Teacher Education\n
History Teacher Education\n
Geography Teacher Education\n
Information Technology Teacher Education\n\n
Graduate programs:\n
M.Ed. in Mathematics Education\n
M.Ed. in Literature Education\n
M.Ed. in Education Management\n\n
Research of School of Education focus on innovation in education in Mekong Delta, South of Viet Nam.\n
The School of Education includes nine academic departments, one center and one High school:\n\n
Department of Elementary Teacher Education\n
Department of Mathematics Teacher Education\n
Department of Physics Teacher Education\n
Department of Chemistry Teacher Education\n
Department of Biology Teacher Education\n
Department of Vietnamese Linguistic &amp; Literature Teacher Education\n
Department of History Teacher Education\n
Department of Geography Teacher Education\n
Department of Psychology in Education</item>

        <item>
Vision \n\n
By 2022, the Department of Physical Education of Can Tho University will become one of the training, scientific research and organization of the best quality movements in the Mekong Delta region, contributing to sustainable quality improvement section for Can Tho University.\n\n

History of development\n\n
The Department of Physical Training and Sports was formed in 1976, the subject was paired with the Military Department called the Military Department.\n
1984: Department of Physical Education under the training department.\n
1987: Department of Physical Education under the Board of Directors.\n
1996: Renamed the Department of Physical Education.\n\n
Mandates\n
1. Teaching physical education for non-major education students at CTU.\n
2. Training of specialized education teachers.\n
3. Teaching physical education for students in the education and training system of the VLS and the links inside and outside CTU.\n
4. Scientific research in the sports field.\n
5. Organizing sports activities for the whole school.\n
6. Fostering regularly to update knowledge and information for high school physical education and sports teachers in areas of special needs.\n\n
In addition, the Department also guides, trains and organizes students to compete in national sports tournaments with 01 volleyball team of CTU, 01 CTU student football team and table tennis and badminton teams. all subjects and ages\n
Taking on the work of education and training of the whole school, the Department now has 01 specialized education major with about 300 specialized students. Lecturers teaching specialized subjects, Badminton, Table Tennis, Martial Arts, Tennis Handball, ...\n\n

Human resources\n
As of 08/2018, the total number of staff of the Department of Physical Education currently has 21 officials, including 06 female cadres.</item>

        <item>
National Preparatory Department has the following training systems:\n\n
- Training pre-university classes 4, A, B, C and D including 02 training systems: regular and pre-selected; Every year there are about 250 students. In one year of study, pre-university students will learn according to the unified program and the regulation of "Pre-university training" of the Ministry of Education and Training (each block consists of 06 to 08 subjects) . In addition to 3 major subjects of Block A (Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry), Block B (Mathematics, Chemistry, Biology), Block C (Literature, History, Geography), Block D (Mathematics students, Literature, English, students also have to study Vietnamese, Informatics, English, Citizen Education, Physical Education in order to meet the comprehensive education for students.\n
- Training classes to supplement the knowledge for students to be considered for direct recruitment of 22 districts of especially poor, remote, border and island areas in the Mekong River Delta; Every year there are about 1000 students. In one year of study, students with direct admission will study in 02 blocks (Natural and Humanities Division) according to the program and own training regulations of Can Tho University. Nature Division study subjects: Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry, Biology and Informatics; Socialist humanities block of subjects: Literature, History, Geography, English and Informatics.</item>
        <item>Dormitory A</item>
        <item>Dormitory B</item>


    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="imgs">

        <item>0</item>
        <item>@drawable/cit</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_eco</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_law</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_bio</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_fish</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_engi</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_env</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_natu</item>
        <item>@drawable/admin</item>
        <item>@drawable/learn_center</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_pol</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_soci</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_school</item>
        <item>@drawable/physical</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_preuni</item>

    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="buildings_name">
        <item>Select a destination…</item>
        <item>College of Information &amp; Communication Technology</item>
        <item>College of Economics</item>
        <item>School of Law</item>
        <item>College of Agriculture &amp; Applied Biology</item>
        <item>College of Aquaculture &amp; Fisheries</item>
        <item>College of Engineering Technology</item>
        <item>College of Environment &amp; Natural Resources</item>
        <item>College of Natural Sciences</item>
        <item>Administration Building</item>
        <item>Learning Resource Center</item>
        <item>School of Political Science</item>
        <item>School of Social Sciences &amp; Humanities</item>
        <item>School of Education</item>
        <item>Department of Physical Education</item>
        <item>School of Pre-University</item>
        <item>Dormitory A</item>
        <item>Dormitory B</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>